A-chan, what happened today?
あちゃん、今日どうしたんですか?
I had a consultation today...
今日相談があって...
Huh, something...
え、なんか...
what?
なに?
Stop for a second.
ちょっとやめて
Throw in some serious stuff.
深刻なのを投げて
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'd like to consult...
相談したいんですけど...
what?
何?
Talking about work...
仕事関係の話で...
Yes, that's right.
うん、だよね
I can't go back to Teisy
テイジーに帰れなくて
...
Are you worried about not being able to go back to Teisy?
テ イジーに帰れないのが 悩みって感じ?
I agree.
そうですね
What, today?
え、今日それ?
Oh, that?
あ、それ?
That's it.
それだけなんだね
As for my worries.
悩みとしては
The biggest problem.
一番の悩み
It's me, when Nacha contacted me.
俺さ、 なちゃから連絡したときに
That's what I thought, but I guess it's the fact that I can't go back to Taiji that worries me.
って 思ったけど テイジーに帰れないっていうのが 悩みか
Huh, is that what you mean because the people around you can't go home?
え、それ、周りが帰れないから そう いうこと?
Seniors around me...
周りの先輩とか...
I'm also curious about what the seniors around me think.
周りの先輩たちの 目も気になる
I'll just say it a little bit.
俺、ちょっと つまり言うけど
The senpai genre is probably scary from now on.
先 輩ってジャンルは 多分、これからしたら怖いんだけど
I think he's just preparing or something.
準備 とかしてるだけだと思うから
Looks like I'm back.
帰 らしい
I've been going there all the time.
ずっと行ってるし
Just because I can't finish my work doesn't mean I can't go home.
だって仕事が終わらないから 帰れないわけじゃない
Even though it's over, there's still some atmosphere.
終わっててもちょっと雰囲気がある
That's true though.
そうなんですけどね
So, I just asked everyone, what do you want?
だし、ちょっと俺が みんなに どこがじゃあ 欲しい?
I'll be the first to go home starting next week.
来週明けから俺が 一番最初に帰るから
Did you hear me just now?
今、聞こえてた?
Yeah.
うん
Maybe I'm always working some kind of overtime.
たぶん、俺もいつも 何だかの残業してるもんね
Yeah.
うん
I'll be the first to go home.
俺が最初に帰るから
So, as I say to everyone, just come back as an adult.
で、 ちょっとみんなに ちょうど大人帰ってくれて 言うように
Because I will.
する から
I'm totally alone in my work.
全然一人のことやってるんだよ
Really, that's not all, is it?
ほんと、それだけでないよね?
hey.
ね
I was really excited, but I lost out a bit.
めっちゃドキドキしてきたのに ちょっと損したわ
Well, certainly.
まあ、確かに
If that's the case, then that's it.
そういうことなら じゃあ、あれだわ
I'm glad I didn't have a private room like this before.
別に こんな個室っていうか 来た前でよかったね
yes.
そう
It looked really serious so I thought it would be okay.
すげえ深刻そうだから大丈夫かなと思ったよ
I couldn't get a rental meeting room, so I ended up coming to a hotel.
貸し会議室とか取れなかったし なんか ホテル来ちゃったけど
hey.
ね
However, it was okay to stay at a hotel even though it wasn't working.
しか もダメ元でホテルってさ オッケーだったりは
That's why I thought it was that serious.
だからそんな深刻なのかなと思ったけど て
Well, if you think about it rationally, this situation is not good.
か、 理性考えたら結構この状況 良くないからね
surely.
確かに
Hotel.
ホテル
At the hotel.
ホテルに
Well then, stop being serious and go into holiday mode.
じゃあちょっと俺の 真面目モード一回やめて 休日モードやって
good?
いい?
it's okay.
大丈夫 です
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Are you relieved?
安心しました?
Senpai, are you relieved?
先輩安心しました?
Feel safe here.
ここ安心して
rest assured.
安心してください
It's okay if you go home early.
早く帰れば大丈夫
It's my first time doing Nacchan's Sasono outside of the office.
なっちゃんのさその 会社の外でやるの初めて
I can't come to work like this.
これで 会社来ちゃダメよさすがに
As expected.
さすがに
it is.
それは
I think it's leg burn.
足バーンって思うね
Do you usually dress like this?
普段この格好してるの?
I usually do it.
普段はしてます
I usually only see her sitting, so I don't know much about her, but she looks pretty good.
普段 座ってる姿しか見ないから あんま分かんないけど 結構身
Long: It's expensive.
長 高いもんね
Is there a second half of 160?
160 後半とかある?
there is.
あります
style?
スタイル?
Maybe it's just me, but it's a little different when we're alone in a hotel.
俺だけかもしれないけど ホテルに2人だと ちょっといつもと
I feel different.
違う 気分になってる
As I mentioned earlier, the place where I consult is a hotel.
さっきもさらっと 言ったけど 俺が相談乗る場所はホテルって
I told you so.
言 ったじゃん
I just went because I didn't have much space anymore.
俺 もう あまりにも場所なかったから 行っただけなんだけど
picture?
え?
Didn't you think so?
とか 思わなかった?
If that's the case, I guess it's okay. I guess there's nothing that's okay.
そうなら大丈夫かな 大丈夫ってのは なんもないかな
Nothing
なん もない
I'm just talking here, A-chan is cute.
ここ だけの話さ あちゃん可愛いじゃん
thank you.
ありがとうございます
But it's a holiday, and I'm not a senior at the company, so you understand that?
でも 休日だから 会社の先輩じゃないから それはわかる?
I think it's really cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いって思う
I've always thought about it a little bit
普段からちょっと思ったけど
Nacchan, now that I think about it, is that happening now?
な っちゃんそういえば 今あれなの?
Are you doing any exercise on your day off or today?
休みの日とか 今日もそうだけど 運動とか今やってるの?
I do it occasionally.
たまにしてます
Do you feel like you've been training a lot?
結構鍛えてる方ではあるって感じ?
My legs and feet are a bit less muscular than those who don't do it, though.
やってない人よりかは 足とかも だ いぶ 筋肉質じゃないけど
These are the feet of someone who has been exercising regularly.
ちゃん と運動してた人の足だもん
So, does your stomach feel closed?
で、お腹とかは 閉まってる感じ?
I'll check then.
じゃあ確認するわ
Isn't it closed already?
もう閉まってない?
Wow, it's closed, really.
すごい 閉まってるね、本当に
Even when I smile, it closes shut.
笑ったときもキュッて閉まってる
If you don't like it, say it as soon as possible.
嫌だったら早いうちに 嫌だって言ってるね
yes.
はい
Nacchan, how many cups is this?
なっちゃん、これ何カップあんの?
C cup?
Cカップ?
C cup Anno.
Cカップあんの
Don't you know that people often see you outside when you're dressed like this?
こんな格好だと 外でよく見られたり知らない?
No, not that much?
いや、そんな あんまり?
Do you think it hurts?
痛 いと思う?
Maybe so.
そうかもしれないです
Aren't you tired?
疲れてない?
You have such a beautiful body, really.
すごい綺麗な体してるんだね 本当に
Is it okay to move your body a little?
体はちょっと動いてみて 大丈夫?
Her body is beautiful, and so is her face.
体も綺麗だし、顔も綺麗だもんね
Try lowering it.
下出してみて
Shall we do it before?
前にやるか
After all, I know who my ex is.
元の人先ってやっぱり知ってる
Well, it's not okay.
え、いいんじゃなくて
I know it because I laugh.
笑いでやっぱり知ってるから
Yeah.
うん
No, it's seriously disgusting
いや、マジで 気持ち悪
stomach.
い
It really shakes me up.
め っちゃ震えるじゃん
Yeah.
うん
I'm keeping it clean.
綺麗にしてるんだ
Your voice was coming out.
声出てたね
Was it nearby?
近くあった?
Yeah.
ええ
Do you have it?
持ってるかい?
I don't have it.
持ってない
Don't have one?
持 ってない?
Do you know anything?
何か分かる?
You know what to massage, right?
マッサージするものってのは知ってるでしょ?
I know.
知ってます
Are you tired?
疲れてるのかな?
Now, let's give it a massage.
これでさ、 マッサージしてみようか
No hands?
手とかいない?
There are quite a lot of different parts of the body, but I guess which part feels the most disgusting?
結構いろんな全身 今当てたけどさ どこが一番気持ち悪いとか
there were?
あ った?
Or if there's anything I can't do yet, please let me know.
とか、まだやり足りないとことか あったら 教えて
Where is it not enough?
や り足りないとこ?
Yeah, I guess I'm not doing enough.
うん、やり足りないとことか
Something like Kuri?
く りーとか?
Cream or something?
くりーとか?
I don't know.
分かんない
i don't know?
知らない?
This one too I like this song. Did you do this?
これもさ この曲好きなんだけどさ これやったの?
I don't know about it, I don't realize how tight it is
知られてないの すごい締まりが 自覚ない
Feels good but doesn't hurt
気 持ちいいけど痛くない
I don't know if you realize it or not, but it's really tight.
自 覚ないか分かんないけど すごい締まっているよ
It's all messed up, but it's all messed up.
く ちゃくちゃになってるけど くちゃくちゃになってる
Suddenly, it feels good, but it feels so deep
いき なり奥 気持ちいいけど 気持ち
Good It feels a little good I'm very good It feels really good though
いい ちょっと気持ちいい 非常に得意な すごい気持ちいいけど
weak point?
苦 手?
Yes, you're not good at it, right?
そう、苦手でしょ
Can I just stand there for a while?
ちょっと 立ちばっかやっていい?
Ma-chan, just come down here. Come up and put your hands on the bed.
まーちゃん、ちょうどここ降りてさ 上ってきて ベッドに手をつ
That's right, stick your butt out a little bit.
いて そうそう お尻をちょっと突き出して め ちゃ
Lay down
く ちゃ伏せる
I was standing all the time from behind, and my waist was so tight.
後 ろから 立ちばっかだったり 腰のくびりすごい
I did it with this feeling
こんな 気持ちでしやがった
Does anyone at work know?
会 社で知ってる人いる?
I'm not there
いないです
feeling
気 持ち
Okay, it's okay, it doesn't hurt.
いい 大丈夫、痛くない
Feels good
気 持ちいい
it hurts
痛 い
This isn't the time to really watch this, so I let it out.
こんな マジマジで見てる場合じゃなくて 出しちゃった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Aren't you angry?
怒 ってない?
Yes, it's true, it wasn't much at all, but with momentum
うん 本当 ちょっと 全然なかったけど 勢いで
OK?
Did it feel good?
気 持ちよかった?
It felt good
気持ちよかった
Don't tell everyone
み んなで言わないで